
DESCRIPTION
    [1] Install FSRM on Local server
        Install FSRM on the local server and import the FileGroup definitions and a screen template.
        Check to see if FSRM is already installed, install if not.
        Add SMTP server, admin email address that will be used to recieve the alerts and From address
    
    [2] Detect all Mapped drives on Domain
        Prompt for a Domain Controller, search and list all drives which have been mapped via GPO.
     
    [3] Install FSRM on Remote server
        Install FSRM and imports the FileGroup definitions and a screen template on a remote server in the domain once specified.
        Check to see if FSRM is already installed, install if not.
        Add SMTP server, admin email address that will be used to recieve the alerts and From address
    
    [4] Set Email Config 
        Change the email configuration settings for SMTP server, defualt receipt address and the From address for a local or Remote server.
        
    [5] Protect File share on Local server
        Update the lcoal FSRM server with new File Screens to protect Shared/Mapped drive folder paths.
    
    [6] Protect File Share on Remote server
        Update a Remmote FSRM server with new File Screens to protect Shared/Mapped drive folder paths.
    
    [7] Test
        Test the setup of the FSRM server, which will send an email after protecting the folder c:\RansomShareTest and adding a known bad file name.
     
    [8] Update Definitions
        Update the crypto definitions on a local or remote server. Useful when a new variant with new extensions  
	appears in the wild. Add a new definition to ransomware_identifiers.txt and choose this option.
    



